{
    "id": "cc90910f9c5b423784e1ba37ba8b34ad",
    "title": "Phrases Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He was a man ................................................ great wealth.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "of",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "89d54b3931084063883c49c6191f452f"
        },
        {
            "question": "The principal was an old man ............................................ friendly disposition.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "of",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7a89c13e011d43a98d67427f9811f300"
        },
        {
            "question": "The workers belonged to a tribe dwelling ................................................. the hills.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "in",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6254ef466f5d46c4830c667258b4be2c"
        },
        {
            "question": "There I met a boy .............................................. red hair.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "in",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0ba91a8ff8a94d8ba691710cba134bab"
        },
        {
            "question": "Only a man with plenty of money can buy a car ................................................. such beauty and power",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "with",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8141a3b4a60b4febbefb84318e009ffe"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was a young man ............................................... great promise.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "with",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "518fce70edd94657a0ad87dc57c802b5"
        },
        {
            "question": "He wore a turban made ............................................ gold.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "with",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "90394264509c481ba5d7c6f685434031"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ran .................................................. great speed.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "with",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "618d3b4aa0604c5190f0eecbc48f8db5"
        },
        {
            "question": "You can buy it ................................................. all places.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b584e59edd7c4ef28841df0c49702b28"
        },
        {
            "question": "He replied ..................................................... a very rude manner.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "with",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "00d7eb89daff43afab9764dc0326af99"
        }
    ]
}